Baby , were you dreaming again ?
Baby .
Were you dreaming the same thing again ?
Samantha .
I don 't know what else to do .
Sam !
Come on , Sam .
Come with me .
Your mom is dead now , Sam .
You don 't have to pretend I 'm your dad anymore , Sam .
Come on , beautiful .
TAXI
BOARDING HOUSE
Excuse me , sir , where is number 23 ?
Number 23 ? It 's usually next to number 22 , miss .
Yes , right .
The house numbers here aren 't in order .
People are too lazy to sort the numbers when they move here .
- It 's crowded . - What house are you looking for ?
The boarding house , sir .
Boarding house ?
There is one .
The rented boarding house .
It 's at the end of the road . You have to pass by the graveyard .
Sorry , miss , I didn 't mean to scare you .
When you pass by that big tree , you have to say a greeting .
Why ?
It 's mandatory for newcomers like you , miss .
Unless it 's us , the locals . We 're already strong enough .
- Maybe they 're bored . - Thank you , sir .
Miss , there 's also a room for rent in the back of this house .
The house is nice , big , cool and cheap .
- That 's your house , Din . - Always talking nonsense .
Don 't reveal my secret !
- So ? - Thank you , sir .
Yes .
In front of a beautiful woman like that !
- Just focus on the game ! - Seriously !
Are you the one calling me ?
- I 'm Mrs. Yanti . - Samantha .
Is that it ?
This is the first floor . It 's for boys only .
It 's quiet now because they 're in college or work .
Some may still be sleeping .
This place used to be that .
Mangkujiwo batik factory .
The occupants were the landlord 's children and the princesses .
Sir !
Sir , I don 't mind if I have to repeat from the initial title assistance .
Rather than me continuing the same topic with a bad result , it 'll be a waste .
It 's better if I start a new topic that I understand .
What do you know about dreams ?
Don 't worry , sir .
I have a lot of references and textbooks that will support my new topic .
I guarantee that within a week , I will finish chapter one ,
and I could continue chapter two .
So I hope tomorrow you and I can ...
Don 't make a schedule out of your ass !
- Two weeks , sir . - Don 't you dare to control me !
Sir .
This is a painting of Raden Ndoro Ayu Sukma Rahimi Mangkujiwo .
She is the great-granddaughter of Panembahan Wiryo Sakti Mangkujiwo .
This painting was made when she was young , but she still looks the same , even now .
Sam , do you like to pray ?
Never mind , it 's okay .
What is this plate for ?
Who put dirty dishes carelessly here ?
Ma 'am ! Please take care of the empty plate !
Are you going to rent a room here ? Be careful or you 'll be just like me .
It has been too long and convenient to the point that you can 't get out .
Dinda .
Sam .
Cool , are you selling it ? Can I buy it ?
Take a look in my room later , okay ?
- Bye . - Bye .
This floor has been closed for a long time by the owner .
So don 't try to enter , okay ?
There aren 't many rules here , but still , you have to follow them .
I mean , it is a boarding house . You 're living in someone else 's house .
There are ten rooms here .
But there are only two bathrooms .
So you have to be willing to queue .
However , if you 're desperate and can 't hold it back ,
you can use the bathroom in the lower ground .
That one .
I 'll get the key for the front door , right , ma 'am ?
I have night classes , so I might go home around 11 p.m. or even midnight .
Yes .
This room is intentionally made bigger than the others ,
but it has the same price .
Unless you bring your own television , computer , or air conditioner .
Then the price is different because you have to pay for the electricity .
This is an antique Mangkujiwo mirror . Not all rooms have it .
Very nice .
- Buzz off . - Damn you .
Joe , I 'll be going , okay ?
What 's wrong with you ? Why did you change your thesis title ?
Dream paradigm ? What the hell is that ?
At least I can talk a lot with my girlfriend again . That 's why .
Gung , you have to graduate first ,
then you can read the meaning of your girlfriend 's dreams one by one .
Whatever . What did you get ?
Was it hard looking for this place ?
Not really , ma 'am , but the entrance is like a maze .
Ma 'am , is it okay if I pay the fee tomorrow ?
It 's okay .
You 're from Jakarta , right ?
Why are you renting a room in a boarding house ?
My parents died .
I am alone .
This house has a lot of history , right ?
Yes , that 's right .
A few years ago , there was a big fire here .
It 's the building next door .
It used to be a batik factory
and this building was the dormitory .
Were there a lot of casualties ?
This third floor is for girls only , no boys allowed .
It 's forbidden .
If the dream repeats itself and it 's the same dream ,
then you shouldn 't let it be , Gung .
You 'd better read this book .
In my opinion , your girlfriend 's dream is too much .
Usually , it doesn 't come from the subconscious anymore ,
but from another world .
Read the book , it 's good .
You 're crazy .
How did you get your hands on this kind of book ?
Your collections are weird .
It 's a shame that I can 't see the haunted tree near the graveyard .
You shouldn 't believe what people say so easily .
Are there people who call it a Kuntilanak tree ?
Seriously .
Kuntilanak ?
Kuntilanak is a made-up story by the elders when I was young .
My grandma used to scare me .
When I was being naughty and wandering around after dusk ,
my grandma would say , " Be careful , or you 'll be kidnapped by a Kuntilanak . "
Seriously .
Did you know ?
Kuntilanak giggles like this .
You sounded like one .
If you hear Kuntilanak close to you ,
it means that she 's far away .
But if the sound is getting farther away ,
that means she 's close by .
Wait .
Didn 't you say Kuntilanak doesn 't exist ? Why did you say ...
Kuntilanak can also be called with a song like this .
Near midnight
You will
Disappear
Don 't get up from your pillow
Be careful not to show yourself
I 'm in the middle of my rage
I sent out djinns and demons
Be the messenger
Don 't bring
Death
What 's wrong ? Are you scared ?
Do you believe Kuntilanak exists ?
There 's no such thing . It 's just a myth , a mystical story .
Besides , if I was the one calling her , even if I make myself hoarse ,
it would be impossible for the Kuntilanak to come .
The only people who can call the Kuntilanak
are the ones with power .
Miss !
Miss , there 's someone looking for you .
Tasya , get inside ! It 's already evening !
Yes , Mom .
Yes , I 'm on my way .
STUFFED PANCAKE
It was dark .
There was something burning behind me .
There were three things in front of me .
I was holding a plate ,
a rock and a scissor .
The theory is that dark colors in dreams are linked with fear and anxiety .
Was there any blue color ?
Blue ?
The scissor was kind of blue .
Also , I always screamed just before I woke up .
I have a strange hunch , Gung .
The residents around my boarding house said there 's a tree with a Kuntilanak .
I 'm so confused .
You 've been repressing a lot of feelings lately .
How long are you going to treat me this way , Sam ?
I don 't know how I could make you forgive me , Sam .
I want to go home .
Keep going ! Yes !
Just drop me off here , Gung .
Why do you have to stay here ? It 's hard to even park .
It 's cheap and it 's just for a while .
My savings are about to run out . I have to find a part-time job .
Don 't worry . I 'll look out for your car .
It 's my job to look out for cars here .
But remember , don 't take too long . No more than an hour , okay ?
You could offend other residents .
Unless you grease some palms .
- Sure , keep an eye on it . - Yes .
Damn , that girl could be my third wife .
Don 't look at it , Gung .
Why ?
Just don 't look at it .
No need to go in , I don 't want to offend the others .
Okay , I 'll be going .
Gung , don 't look at the tree , okay ?
Yes .
You have positive and negative energy . You , and even him .
This room has a lot of negative energy ,
not to mention the antiques around .
But Fon , isn 't it ...
I see two in the back ,
but don 't worry ,
as long as we don 't disturb them , they won 't disturb us either .
- Screw you . Now I can 't sleep . - Damn it . Now I can 't sleep .
Hey , new kid ! Can I see your palm ?
What ? You promised you 'd tell my fortune !
You 're wasteful .
You often feel lonely in the crowd , right ?
Yes .
Everyone can be wasteful and lonely .
Don 't be fooled .
What 's your deal ?
Sorry that I 'm paying today , ma 'am .
It 's okay .
Sam , this chair shouldn 't face the corner of the wall .
It 's forbidden .
Why ?
Nothing , it 's just that you shouldn 't . Okay ?
Look at it .
Well ?
In my opinion , there are several possibilities , Gung .
It 's a picture of a root and a root is connected to a tree .
- Was there a tree around it ? - I took it from a tree .
Why does the tree have tiles ?
Tiles , my ass . Continue !
But the tree is quite big .
It 's surrounded by a fence and it 's in the middle of the graveyard .
If I had to live in a boarding house where I have to pass a graveyard ,
then no , thank you .
Continue .
The room is quite big , but a bit old .
There are three floors .
Free laundry as well .
Sam said ...
Who is the owner , again ?
It 's ...
the Mangkujiwo family .
Mangkujiwo ?
Agung , it isn 't a family . They were cultists from back then .
They still exist , ma 'am .
The landlady is the owner .
That 's weird .
As far as I know , there was no one left to continue the cult .
If I 'm not mistaken , they had a lot of factories .
But now ,
they 're gone .
The residents and the police burned it to the ground .
They hated heretical cultists .
Maybe you heard it wrong .
Got you , Gung .
Don 't forget to take the medicine , okay ?
Yes , ma 'am .
It 's just influenza . Tree ?
Kuntilanak lives in a tree .
Kuntilanak , my ass . Here 's Kuntilanak !
But you 're right .
The residents said that it 's the place for Kuntilanak .
Kuntilanak , here .
I have the picture .
Many people say that Kuntilanak is half-woman , half-horse .
Here 's the picture that I have .
No , I don 't want to see it .
There are a lot of Kuntilanak in Sumatra and Borneo .
Some have children , some like to take babies .
In East Java , misguided people use them for pesugihan to make them rich .
- Hey , man . - What ?
I have a friend .
His mom used to tell me
that a ghost ...
Shut it .
Kuntilanak lives in a tree .
But if she wants to come out , then it 's from somewhere else .
Out ? What do you mean ?
Out into our world .
She does live in a tree .
But if she wants to come out ,
she goes through certain mediums .
It could be from a cupboard , a chest , antiques ,
just about anything .
Let me see .
If it 's true that the tree behind the fence is a Kuntilanak tree ...
Wait .
If it 's true that Sam 's boarding house has a Kuntilanak ...
Then ...
where did she come from ?
Try one more .
IQ fight .
Ani 's mom has five children . AA , II , UU , EE . Who is the last one ?
- Definitely EE . - Wrong .
- II ? - Wrong .
Once more . Ani 's mom has five children . AA , II , UU , EE . Who is the last one ?
- OO . - Idiot . It 's Ani !
Great .
You 're such a joker , Gung .
Sam , wait !
You don 't have to drop me off . Aren 't you going to meet your advisor ?
Why are you so noisy in the middle of the night ?
What ?
Yes , I bring men here . I bring men here every day !
So what ?
Do you have a problem ?
Sorry .
Sorry , I just want to sleep .
Sleep ?
Sleep ? Do you want me to put you to sleep forever ?
Look .
You are the new kid .
- Near midnight - Don 't misbehave .
- You will - What do you want ?
Disappear
Don 't get up
From your pillow
Be careful not to show yourself
I 'm in the middle of my rage
I sent out djinns and demons
Be the messenger
Don 't bring
Death
Come on , baby , let it go .
Let 's just look for another place to stay . Okay ?
Why did you bring a man here ?
It 's not allowed . Go away .
Sam !
What 's wrong ?
Sam .
What 's the matter ?
Next time , you should use a condom .
If you don 't have it , just ask me .
Damn that new kid . We were just getting started !
Hey , where are we going ? My head hurts !
Let 's look for an hourly hotel . There are a lot of them .
My nosebleed won 't stop !
Hey !
They don 't pay again .
What a terrible habit they have .
I 'm going to poop .
MELATY MOTEL
Sit there . Give it to me .
Where are you going ?
Shut up , I 'm going to buy wine first .
Hey , don 't leave Mawar alone . Mawar is afraid to be alone .
What the hell ? Are you a child ?
That 's ...
Did you hear that ?
There is someone laughing .
But it sounds very far away .
You 're too fussy . I 'm going .
Hey , come on !
The victim was allegedly having fun in the hotel room when the accident occurred .
The death is unusual because the victim was found with the head turned backward .
The victim , Mawar Sibarani ,
was last seen leaving her boarding house on the outskirts of Jakarta .
I 'm Mini Resmala for Silat .
Is it done ? Okay .
It 's enough , right ?
Yes , I said that they were really drunk .
It 's their own doing . They were drunk , why did they ride a motorbike ?
How come Mawar 's face looked like that , ma 'am ?
I don 't know .
- It 's complicated . - Let 's go back .
There must be something wrong .
What 's the matter ?
Let 's talk in my room . You can also see my merchandise in the meantime .
Ndoro Ayu , I 'm sorry , have you heard the news ?
Who could have known about life and death ?
- Yesterday , I wished for her to die . - What ?
Nothing .
I took it from Celak .
If you go to Kuta or Legian , you won 't find it .
It 's cheap . I 'll pick a good one for you .
You have one too ?
Cool , right ?
Mrs. Yanti said that there are only four mirrors here .
Four ?
Here , your room , Ratih 's room and ...
Second floor , maybe ?
Who knows .
Anyway , if you buy three , I 'll give you four chains for free .
Why were you throwing up yesterday ?
If you want to talk , you could always talk to me .
We 're both children of broken families .
A woman as beautiful as you
rent a room with only a few items .
Then you fought with Mawar .
Probably because you were fighting with your parents .
Right ?
My stepdad .
I don 't want to live with him .
My mom recently passed away .
Your boyfriend ?
I have one .
But well ...
I love him .
But I don 't know if I could believe him .
Sam !
Someone is looking for you ! It 's Agung !
Are you okay ?
I 've been calling you , but you didn 't pick up .
Sorry , I left my cell phone in my room .
I heard the news earlier on television .
It 's so scary .
Luckily , it didn 't happen here .
What 's that ?
Nothing . It was a mosquito bite . It 'll be gone soon .
Yes , a mosquito like me .
Dinda , his name is Agung .
- Agung . - Dinda .
Don 't worry , I 'll take care of your girl .
Look , Gung .
A WOMAN DIED WITH HEAD TURNED BACKWARD AND DAMAGED FACE
Your girlfriend 's boarding house doesn 't seem right .
This is the news I saw on television earlier . Is there any connection ?
Of course , there is .
It 's in this magazine .
Here . This person died because of Kuntilanak .
All of their heads turned backward .
Sam ?
- What are you doing ? - Nothing . I just ...
- Nothing ? Your face is so pale . - No , I 'm okay .
- Are you sure you don 't want my company ? - No !
Relax , Sam . I don 't want you to be alone .
Don 't be like that .
The room next to yours was recently occupied by a dead person .
It 's not good .
Near midnight
You will
Disappear
Don 't get up
From your pillow
Be careful not to show yourself
I 'm in the middle of my rage
I sent out djinns and demons
Be the messenger
Don 't bring
Death
What the fuck ?
What is that ?
What did you sing ?
Fuck !
What did she do to me ?
Oh my God !
In my room ...
What 's wrong with him ?
Whatever . Don 't talk about him anymore .
Dude , pay the parking fee !
Damn it , no money again .
I 'm going home .
Sam ?
Did you hear strange voices from my room ?
What 's wrong with you ?
I don 't know .
I doubted it before , Ndoro Ayu .
But then someone is killed again .
Luckily , the accident happened in Kuningan .
It 's far from here , Ndoro .
Then why did you sing " Durmo " ?
You know you shouldn 't sing Durmo recklessly .
I 'm sorry , Ndoro Ayu , I was presumptuous .
It 's destiny . Durmo chose her .
I want to see that girl .
Alfond is dead !
- They said his car slipped . - Did you hear ?
His face is messed up and his head is turned backward !
Like Mawar ?
Alfond ...
is dead ?
Alfond is dead
because of me .
That 's Sam , Ndoro .
Sam .
Let me introduce you . This is Ndoro Ayu Sukma .
Why are you wearing a scarf in the middle of a hot afternoon like this ?
Sam !
Sorry , who are you ?
You don 't need a mortal like him .
Gung ?
Good afternoon .
Sam , do you feel cold after you 're dreaming ?
Cold ?
I mean cold from the inside , not from the outside .
Wank , don 't ask weird questions .
I 'm serious , Gung .
According to the Primbon I read ,
if you often feel cold after you 're dreaming ,
that means something passed by .
But if you feel hot , that means something came inside .
Sorry , Sam .
Do you often think of your mom after you 're dreaming ?
No .
You 're so annoying .
Wank .
What ?
- Don 't ask her questions like that . - It 's important , Gung .
If it 's true , it means that Sam 's trauma is very deep .
Yes , I know .
Our relationship is strained .
I also got the Mangkujiwo book .
It 's mysterious .
She 's looking at it now .
I want to help , you know .
THE STRONG OWN
" The strong own . "
The strong own ?
I have a class . Thank you , Wank .
Okay , Sam .
Sam ! It 's your fault !
Sam , wait !
Iwank was just running his mouth . Don 't take it personally , okay ?
Sam .
I always feel guilty .
You never look at my eyes every time you talk to me .
What 's wrong with you ?
You 've been so distant from me lately !
What 's the point of forgiving me if you never forget about it ?
Gung , the problem isn 't you anymore ! I need time !
Yes , but until when ? I can 't wait forever .
I need some clarity , Sam .
Now you want clarity ?
Where are you when I need you ?
- Sam ... - You knew my mom was sick !
You also knew I had a bad feeling all the time ,
but you still went with your friends !
Sam ...
I 'm sorry , Sam .
When my mom died ,
where were you ?
Now you ask for clarity ?
I should be the one who asked you that !
So you still remember everything .
What should I do , Sam ?
What else can I do ?
Whatever , Gung . Leave me alone .
Sam !
Sam , I love you .
Leave me alone .
- Sam . - Leave me alone !
Near midnight
You will
Disappear
Don 't get up
From your pillow
Be careful not to show yourself
I 'm in the middle of my rage
I sent out djinns and demons
Be the messenger
Don 't bring
Death
No , don 't come to him .
Sam ...
Hey ! Come out if you dare !
Ma 'am ?
Maybe he 's staying at Iwank 's house , ma 'am .
He 's not there ?
I don 't know either .
I 'll try to find him later .
You 're welcome . Please give me the updates .
Good afternoon , ma 'am .
You are connected to the voicemail of the number ...
Sam , don 't deny it anymore .
I know you still love him .
Ma 'am , don 't be negative , okay ?
Agung will come home .
Yes , ma 'am .
Good night .
Maybe he 's giving you time for yourself .
Didn 't you ask him that ?
He never acted like this , Din . Never .
Sam .
Gung ?
Help me , Sam .
Where are you ?
Sam .
Gung ?
Forgive me .
- Gung ? - Sam .
Gung ?
Don 't you dare !
Sorry , ma 'am . I heard a voice .
- I thought ... - There 's nothing there !
I 've already told you .
Don 't you even try to open that door . Now go back to your room !
Where the hell are you , Gung ?
I 'm sorry .
I 'm not trying to scare you , but don 't forget to check the hospitals too .
I did , he 's not there .
There has been no news until now .
I don 't get you .
She 's jealous .
Why do you keep asking about Agung ?
I 'm worried .
Do you like my boyfriend ?
What ?
Why did you say that ?
You like him .
From the first time I introduced you two .
From the way you asked about him .
You have a crush on my boyfriend !
What 's wrong with you , Sam ?
Sam !
Sam ?
Near midnight , you will
What 's wrong with you ?
Disappear
Don 't get up
From your pillow
I sent out djinns and demons
Don 't bring
Death
My nosebleed is acting up .
Dinda , you have to go .
You have to go . You could get hurt .
Who 's laughing ?
Screw you .
Really ? Dinda is dead ?
No need to bring it up anymore .
I will take Dinda 's body to her mom in Garut tonight .
Let Dinda rest in peace .
Sam .
Help me , Sam .
Sam ! Why are you still here ?
Dinda 's death is so scary .
Agung is here .
- I want to find him . - You 're crazy !
Sam .
Help .
Sam !
I 'm scared .
Sam .
Sam , I 'm scared .
Help me .
Sam .
I 'm scared .
I 'm scared , Sam .
MANGKUJIWO BATIK FACTORY
Sam , forgive me .
Gung ?
Sam .
Gung !
Gung , what 's wrong with you ?
- Help ! - Gung .
Let 's go .
Gung .
Sam .
Slow down , Sam .
Gung ?
Come on , Gung .
- Gung ? - Let 's go .
Come on , let 's go outside .
Your wound ...
Gung !
Gung . Come on . Let 's go .
It hurts , Sam .
How many times should I tell you ?
You must be able to separate yourself from weak humans .
For decades , Wongso Mangkujiwo has been keeping Kuntilanak as pesugihan .
Here , in this building , we all make sacrifices .
So that the Kuntilanak remains under our influence .
Everyone died when this place burned down .
Mangkujiwo 's lineage stopped there .
I can 't have children .
No one else can pass on the power to summon the Kuntilanak .
But you have the talent .
It 's natural that you 're scared and confused at first .
You couldn 't control the great power within you .
A power that can fulfill all of your wishes .
I didn 't mean to hurt them .
All of your grudges will be avenged .
Any hatred that you send will fall on the head of the person you hate .
You just need to learn and explore the desires deep inside your heart .
The darkest part .
In the end , you 'll get whatever you wish for .
Whatever you want .
Yes , Ndoro Ayu .
Sam .
Don 't listen to her .
- Sam ! - Near midnight
- Sam ! - You will
Sam , wake up ! Sam !
Disappear
- Don 't get up - Sam !
From your
- Sam ! - Pillow
- Be careful not to show yourself - Sam , wake up !
I 'm in the middle of my rage
- Sam ! - I sent out
- Djinns and demons - Sam !
It 's me , Sam !
- Be the messenger - Sam !
Fight , Sam !
Sam , fight it !
Don 't bring
Sam !
I 'm not strong enough , Gung .
- Sam , you can do it ! - Death
You 're strong , Sam !
You can do it , Sam ! Come on , fight !
You 've been through the worst ! You can get through this one too !
Sam !
Sam .
Don 't listen to her .
Accept the fact that you have the talent .
If you want to learn from me , you can gain a lot of wealth .
The strong
own .
No !
I don 't want to pass on the power of calling Kuntilanak !
I will report that you have a pesugihan of Kuntilanak in this place !
Near midnight
You will
Disappear
Don 't get up
From your pillow
- Be careful not to show yourself - Near midnight , you will
- Disappear - I 'm in the middle of my rage
Don 't get up from your pillow
I sent out djinns and demons
- I 'm in the middle of my rage - Be careful not to show yourself
I 'm in the middle of my rage
- Don 't bring death - I sent out djinns and demons
Be the messenger
Don 't bring
Death
I see .
This is my first time .
Because of this little girl .
Ndoro .
Help me , Ndoro . I don 't want to die now , Ndoro .
I 'm not ready to die .
I don 't know what to do .
Break all the mirrors , that 's how she comes out !
Dinda 's room !
One , two , three ...
There are four of them !
Ma 'am ?
Forgive me .
Mrs. Sri ?
Samantha !
Please , Ndoro . I 'm not ready .
Help me . Please , Ndoro .
Help me , Ndoro .
I 'm not ready .
Let 's play in hell , miss .
Let 's go to hell , miss .
- Let 's go to hell , miss . - Let 's play in hell , miss .
- Let 's go , miss . - Let 's go , miss .
Let 's go with us to hell , miss .
Hurry up , miss .
The strong ...
The strong , Sam .
The strong own .
I 'm sorry , Gung .
Sam .
The doctor allowed you to walk ?
I 've found another cheap boarding house in the middle of the city .
Why are you still here ?
Come here , Gung .
The air is really good here .
You never felt it before .